So here we have our skeleton code for the PokemonApp.
这是 Pokemon 应用的代码框架
If we go into app, source, main,
如果深入到 app、src、main、java 层级
java, we have two Java files.
我们能看到两个 Java 文件
MainActivity and HttpHandler.
MainActivity 和 HttpHandler
Let's look at the MainActivity file first.
我们先来看看 MainActivity 文件
The first thing to notice is that you'll see
你首先可能发现
a few red lines in the code, but don't worry.
代码中有一些红色的行 不过别担心
As soon as you finish this practice set those lines should go away.
等你完成这套练习后 那些行将会自动消失
We see that there is a GetPokemon class with a doInBackground at it.
我们发现这个 GetPokemon 类下有 doInBackground
We have an HttpHandler and a string url with this link. Let's click on it.
还有 HttpHandler 以及包含这条链接的 string url 我们点击它
So, here we have the JSON data for each Pokemon,
这里是每个 Pokemon 的 JSON 数据
and each Pokemon will have its respective unique attributes.
每个 Pokemon 都具有各自独特的属性
So for example, it will have an integer attribute called id,
举例而言 它拥有名为 id 的整数属性
a string attribute called num and a couple other attributes.
名为 num 的字符串属性 以及其他几个属性
There is also an attribute type with an array that holds several strings.
这里还有一个 type 属性 它带有一个包含几个字符串的数组
The thing to notice here is that each Pokemon will have a different set of attributes.
值得注意的是 每个 Pokemon 都拥有不同的属性集
And we'll be using its attributes to display in our app.
我们将在应用中显示这些属性
Going back to the MainActivity.
回到 MainActivity 文件中
Let's keep going. There are several TODO tasks for you to do.
我们继续往下看 这里有几个需要执行的 TODO 任务
So just make a request to the URL and create a new JSONObject.
例如 make a request to the URL 以及 Create a new JSONObject
There's also a for loop that will go through all the Pokemons
这里还有一个 for 循环 它将遍历所有 Pokemon
and put them in a list that we'll be using to display over here.
并将它们列入一个将在这里显示的列表中
Next, let's look at our HttpHandler file.
接下来 我们来看看 HttpHandler 文件
Here, there is a method called makeHttpRequest and we will pass in the URL.
这是一个名为 makeHttpRequest 的方法 我们传入 URL
Here is where we make the request to make a connection with the URL.
我们在这里创建连接请求连接这个 URL 地址
Next, let's look in the res file and layout.
接下来 我们进入 res 文件下的 layout
These files are provided for you,
我们已为你提供这些文件
so you don't have to worry about how to display each Pokemon.
所以你不用担心如何显示每个 Pokemon
This is a simple list format that will display each Pokemon.
这是一个简单列表格式 将显示每个 Pokemon
And this is what each list item will have.
这是每个列表项的内容
There is a box for a name,
包括 name 框
an id and a candy.
id 和 candy
These files will organize the information you're parsing into a simple list format.
这些文件会将你解析的信息整理成一个简单列表格式
So in the next few sections,
在接下来的几节课中
we'll be fill in these blanks to
我们将填充这些空白位置
list out all of the Pokemons with three of their attributes.
列出所有 Pokemon 及其三个属性
Their name, their id and their candy.
即 name、id 和 candy
This is what the final product should look like.
最终产品应该就是这样的
You will see that the name is at the top. So, Bulbasaur.
你将看到名称显示在顶部 就是 Bulbasaur
This is their id and this is their candy.
这是 id 这是 candy
And if I scroll down,
向下滚动
you'll find that each Pokemon will have different attributes.
你会发现每个 Pokemon 拥有不同的属性 00:02:44,790 --&gt; 00:00:00,000 现在我们开始吧